Invisv Privacy Policy
=====================

### LAST UPDATED: \[2022.05.15\]

**PRIVACY POLICY**

INVISV, INC. (“**INVISV**,” “**we**,” or “**us**”) wants you to be familiar with how we collect, use and disclose personal information. This Privacy Policy describes our practices in connection with personal information that we collect through:

The website operated by us from which you are accessing this Privacy Policy (the “**Website**”);

Email messages that we send to you that link to this Privacy Policy; and

Offline business interactions you have with us, for example, when you discuss business opportunities with us.

Collectively, we refer to the Website, email messages and offline business interactions as the “**Services**.”

**Personal Information**

“**Personal Information**” is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to an identifiable individual. The Services collect Personal Information, including:

Email address;

**Collection of Personal Information**

We and our service providers collect Personal Information through the Services, for example, when you provide your email address through our Website to receive updates and other communications about our current or future offerings.

We need to collect Personal Information in order to provide the requested Services to you. If you do not provide the information requested, we may not be able to provide these Services. If you disclose any Personal Information relating to other people to us or to our service providers in connection with the Services, you represent that you have the authority to do so and to permit us to use the information in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

**Use of Personal Information**

We and our service providers use Personal Information for the following purposes:

**Providing you with information and materials about our offerings.**

To send you marketing related or informational emails, with information about our services, products and other news about our company.

> Where required under applicable law, we will engage in this activity with your consent. Otherwise, our related processing of your Personal Information will be based on our legitimate business interest to communicate with you upon your request.

**Providing the functionality of the Services and fulfilling your requests.**

To provide the Services’ functionality to you, such as operating the Website;

To respond to your inquiries and fulfill your requests, for example, when you send us questions, suggestions, compliments or complaints, or when you request other information about our Services.

> We will engage in these activities based on our legitimate business interest to provide the Services to you upon your request.

**Accomplishing our business purposes.**

For audits, to verify that our internal processes function as intended and to address legal, regulatory, or contractual requirements;

For fraud prevention and fraud security monitoring purposes, for example, to detect and prevent cyberattacks or attempts to commit identity theft;

For enhancing, improving, repairing, maintaining, or modifying our current products and services, as well as undertaking quality and safety assurance measures;

To protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others;

For compliance with applicable law and regulations. This may include laws outside your country of residence.

> We engage in these activities to comply with a legal obligation and/or based on our legitimate business interests.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

We disclose Personal Information:

**To our third party service providers, to facilitate services they provide to us.**

These can include providers of services such as website hosting, data analysis, fraud prevention, information technology and related infrastructure provision, email delivery, auditing, and other services.

**To our third party advisors.**

We may disclose your Personal Information to our advisors (e.g. auditors, legal counsel, tax advisers and consultants) relating to or in connection with the operation of our business, compliance with our legal, regulatory or contractual obligations and/or your investments with us.

**To law enforcement agencies and other government authorities.**

In order to comply with our legal or regulatory obligations, we may disclose your Personal Information to law enforcement agencies, regulatory or tax authorities and other governmental or public agencies or authorities.

**To third parties in the event of reorganization.**

Your Personal Information may be disclosed to third parties in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, partnership, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).

**Security**

We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization. If you have any questions or concerns regarding the security of your personal information or your interaction with, please notify us in accordance with the _“Contacting Us”_ section below.

**CHOICES AND ACCESS**

**Receiving marketing-related emails from us**.

If you no longer want to receive marketing related emails from us on a going-forward basis, you may opt out by clicking on the unsubscribe link contained in every such email you receive from us. Alternatively, you may notify us of your decision to opt out in accordance with the _“Contacting Us”_ section below.

**Accessing, changing, or deleting your Personal Information.**

If you would like to request to access, correct, update, suppress, restrict, or delete Personal Information, object to or opt out of the processing of Personal Information, or if you would like to request to receive a copy of your Personal Information for purposes of transmitting it to another company (to the extent these rights are provided to you by applicable law), you may contact us in accordance with the “Contacting Us” section below. We will respond to your request consistent with applicable law.

When contacting us, please make clear what Personal Information is subject to your request. We may need to verify your identity before implementing your request. We will respond to your request in compliance with applicable law.

**RETENTION PERIOD**

We retain Personal Information for as long as needed or permitted in light of the purpose(s) for which it was obtained and consistent with applicable law.

The criteria used to determine our retention periods include:

The length of time we have an ongoing relationship with you and provide the Services to you;

Whether there is a legal obligation to which we are subject (for example, certain laws require us to keep records of your transactions for a certain period of time before we can delete them); or

Whether retention is advisable in light of our legal position (such as in regard to applicable statutes of limitations, litigation or regulatory investigations).

**THIRD PARTY SERVICES**

This Privacy Policy does not address, and we are not responsible for, the processing of your personal information by, or other practices of, any third parties, including any third party operating any website or service to which the Services link. The inclusion of a link on the Services does not imply endorsement of the linked site or service.

**Use of Services by MINORS**

The Services are not directed to individuals under the age of sixteen (16), and we do not knowingly collect Personal Information from individuals under 16.

**Jurisdiction and CROSS-BORDER TRANSFER**

Your Personal Information may be stored and processed in any country where we have facilities or in which we engage service providers, and by using the Services you understand that your information may be transferred to countries outside of your country of residence, including the United States, which may have data protection rules that are different from those of your country. In certain circumstances, courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies or security authorities in those other countries may be entitled to access your Personal Information.

**SENSITIVE INFORMATION**

We ask that you not send us, and you not disclose, any sensitive Personal Information (e.g., social security numbers, information related to racial or ethnic origin, political opinions, religion or other beliefs, health, biometrics or genetic characteristics, criminal background, or trade union membership) on or through the Services or otherwise to us.

**DO NOT TRACK SIGNALS**

Since we do not track users over time and across third-party web sites or online services, we do not currently respond to browser do-not-track signals.

**UPDATES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY**

The “_Last Updated_” legend at the top of this Privacy Policy indicates when this Privacy Policy was last revised. Any changes will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the Services.

**CONTACTING US**

INVISV, INC., located at 4676 ADMIRALTY WAY #503 MARINA DEL REY, CA 90292, is the company responsible for the collection, use, and disclosure of your Personal Information under this Privacy Policy.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us at legal@invisv.com, or:

4676 ADMIRALTY WAY #503 MARINA DEL REY, CA 90292

If you are located in the EU/EEA and you have concerns regarding the processing of your Personal Information, you may also lodge a complaint with an EU/EEA supervisory authority.

©INVISV 2022-2023
